[bright music]
Hi, son. How are you?
Son, thank you.
Aunt Susan said she already received
the remittance. Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Andre, is there a problem?
Do you have something to tell me?
Is something troubling you, Andre?
That's quite deep, Mom.
I know you very well, son.
Come on, tell me.
Mom,
first of all, I would like to apologize.
I hope you can forgive me.
But I'll also understand
if you get mad at me.
Why? What did you do?
Mom, do you remember what I told
you about the Hollywood Executive?
The project I was supposed to do here?
It wasn't true, Mom.
I was scammed here.
I lost most of your savings.
I thought I would have an opportunity
if I accepted his offer.
But he just ran off with your money.
[soft music]
I'm sorry, Mom.
But don't worry.
I have a part-time job here.
And I'm earning just enough.
After a few months,
I'll be able to return everything
you've worked hard for.
Son, don't worry about it.
It's just money. I can earn it again.
The important thing is
you didn't get hurt by the
person who deceived you.
I see posts on Facebook
where people are getting
randomly attacked by
strangers out of nowhere.
It’s scary.
Most importantly, you're
not the one who was deceitful.
I would be mad at you
if you were the one
cheating or deceiving
others just to make money.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
[soft music]
It's okay, son.
Things happen.
But wait, did I hear it right?
You're going to work
there for a few months?
You're not going back home anytime soon?
That's another thing I want
to discuss with you, Mom.
I won't go back to the
Philippines anytime soon.
Is that even possible? Do you
have the necessary papers?
Andre,
how can you work there if
you don't have legal papers?
There are those who do that here.
They can work even without papers.
I promise, Mom, once I'm
settled here, you can stop working.
I will be the one to provide for you.
Just come home and relax.
Andre, son, listen to me.
Decisions like that
need careful consideration.
You must not be impulsive.
Ask someone you know there.
Approach a lawyer who
knows what you should do.
Consult what’s the
best and right thing to do.
And another thing,
it's not your obligation
to give me a good life.
[soft music]
That's why I'm working hard here
so that I could help you
achieve your dreams.
Andre, you're my only child.
You grew up without a father.
And I know, no matter what,
I can never fill that void.
And I know
you insist on being there because
you're hoping to see your father.
But son, we can't do anything
if he doesn't want to meet you.
And your dream is to write
and direct movies, right?
Didn't you say you were chosen
in a contest in the Philippines?
And they would provide
funding for your film?
Would you just let go of that opportunity?
It's just initial funding, Mom.
That's why I want to work here, to
earn some money and create films.
But it will be very difficult for
you if you don't have legal papers.
[soft music]
And I don't want to go back to the
Philippines if you wouldn't be there.
There’s no reason for me to come home.
I'll just keep on working here.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too, son.
Always take care, okay?
[soft music]
What are you doing with that?
- With what? - The... the air bed.
Oh, I’m just getting ready to
sleep, right? I'm just fixing it up.
Would you rather sleep in a real bed?
Yeah, I would.
Good night.
Mmm...
Wait, were you just asking
me if I would sleep beside you?
I didn’t say that.
[bright music]
I can’t sleep when someone's hugging me.
But -
Do you want to go back to your air bed?
Okay po. Good night po.
What was that?
What was what?
That thing you just said?
I just said okay and good night.
No, after that. Um, after
good night. What was that?
It was like a “pow”?
Oh, yeah. It’s a Filipino thing, "po."
Is it a good Filipino thing?
Yeah, um...
It just means...
It’s like a sign of respect.
“Po” and “opo”.
Okay, um,
well, go to sleep.
[bright music]
I said go to sleep…
"po".
Okay po.
I don’t know how you can
see with those things on.
[bright music]
Proposal?
Did I hear it correctly, bestfriend?
Yes, bestriend.
I'm going to propose to him.
But K-pop is still very young.
That's okay.
Some of my batchmates
got married at eighteen.
But shouldn't you think about it first?
As they say, impatience is a breeding
ground for regrets and mistakes.
It’s not even a month since you two met,
yet you're already talking about marriage?
You probably don't even
know his favorite color yet!
But some people elope and get married only
a few minutes after meeting each other.
And as I explained earlier,
according to the immigration
lawyer I consulted,
the fastest way to get papers in the US
is to marry an American.
So you're marrying him just for the papers?
I thought you were also eligible for
O-1, O-1 and AB-AB?
It’s EB, not AB. Employment-based petition.
Yeah, that’s also an option
but that’s gonna take time.
And I’m not even sure if
I’m qualified enough for that.
Well, you're also not sure
if K-pop will marry you.
There's a greater chance
that he will marry me
compared to other
options the lawyer told me.
That's why be ready, okay?
Really, bestfriend?
What for?
I’m gonna introduce you to Joshua.
Practice what you're going to say.
Then we'll head straight to the proposal.
Oh, I thought you're asking me to
go there and be your maid of honor!
But why do I have to join your proposal?
Of course, you're my witness!
A lot of people propose
in front of huge crowds.
You know, like in the movies?
Let's do it now!
Where is Baby Josh anyway?
Still at work, driving.
Really? What time is it there?
It's almost two in the morning.
Wow! Baby Josh is such a workhorse!
But wait, do you already have a ring?
[bright music]
I'll buy it once he says yes.
Don't be silly, it doesn't work like that!
You should have a ring
first before you propose.
Do you want me to send
you the infinity stones?
Crazy!
Stop it.
Anyway, I have to go. I'm sleepy.
I can't wait for Baby Josh anymore.
I mean... Joshua.
Goodness! This is your fault!
Alright, got to go as
well. Heading to my show.
Bye, bestfriend.
Sorry, I didn’t mean to wake you.
No, no, you’re good. I’m just…
I’m checking the time.
Well,
you’re not getting enough sleep.
You worked until six in
the morning last night. And...
Maybe you should just take a day off.
I'm fine.
Hey, um,
do you think I could get
a driver's license here?
I was just thinking it would be
nice if I could earn more and...
do stuff like food
deliveries or ride sharing.
Just work at the store for right now.
And we'll figure out something later.
There, um...
There is actually something
else I wanted to ask you.
Mmm?
And I completely understand if you’re not…
comfortable.
But, um,
there is something I’ve been
wanting to do for a long time…
with you.
And I completely get it
if you’re not ready but...
you’re the only person
I wanna do this with.
And somehow,
it feels like now is the right time.
[playful music]
Of course, I don’t want to
force you to do anything.
And I completely understand if you’re not…
Maybe you’re tired. Or you're sleepy. Or –
Can I take a shower first?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah?
I’ll…
I’ll be right here.
Whoa!
[playful music]
Bestfriend, please behave.
He’s very sensitive. He easily gets mad.
Hello?
Why would he get mad at this face?
How to prepare for sex
after long abstinence
Bestfriend, please?
He’s only had four hours of sleep.
I don't want to ruin his mood.
I’m serious about this.
Behave, behave, behave.
Well, I just got home from my show.
I’m so sleepy and tired.
And you expect me to be
insincere when dealing with him?
If he doesn't like me, I have
no reason to like him either.
5 tips for having sex
again after a long hiatus
May I just remind you
that this is not about you, okay?
that this is all about me.
You want him to know me, right?
Bestfriend, please?
I just want to introduce
him to some people in my life
before I propose.
Some people?
I'm not just "some people", bestfriend.
I’m the most important person in your life!
Because of that, I don't
want to meet him anymore.
You need to choose.
Me or Baby Josh?
Oh, come on.
Why are you making things difficult for me?
You know how important this is for me.
[playful music]
Lipstick from Mac.
Fine.
And concealer from Sephora.
Where's Baby Josh?
I’m really sleepy.
In the bathroom.
But he'll be here in a minute.
He's coming in.
Just keep quiet, okay?
Let me do the talking.
[playful music]
Hey,
are you okay?
Come here.
Sit beside me.
What?
Why?
Just
sit beside me.
Why am I sitting beside you?
Uh, come over here
and you'll find out.
Can't we...
just go to the bed?
Yeah, we could. But...
it's a lot easier if we just do it here.
Come on. Just give it a try.
Okay.
- I know what's on your mind.
- So you know you're going to like it.
Absolutely not.
Just... do it for me.
No.
Wh… What if that were to leak?
Ah...
This is just for us.
No. I'm...
I’m not interested.
But you already agreed to do this.
I didn’t think you were gonna record us.
What the fuck?
Alright. Aah...
This was a bad idea. I don’t
know what’s wrong with you
but I’m not gonna fall
for any of your fetishes.
Who is that?
That’s my bestfriend.
As in...
"besh."
What?
I've been wanting to introduce
you two for the longest time. And...
I wasn’t sure you were
comfortable or ready yet but
that's what I was talkibng about.
Wait, what were you talking about?
[playful music]
Stop it, bestfriend! You’re so noisy.
Hey!
Oops...
Sorry.
Baby Andre.
Let's eat?
I'm not hungry.
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
If we want this,
us,
whatever it is we’re doing work out,
we have to be a lot clearer in
how we communicate, okay?
Yeah, sorry about that. I, uh...
I think I just, uh...
- Sometimes, I just can be confusing.
- I’m easily confused.
Well, I promise we’re not gonna have
anymore lost in translation moments.
Okay.
Actually, maybe now
is not the best time but…
there’s something I wanted to ask you.
Do you like me?
Is this another lost in translation moment?
I just…
I like you.
And I’m asking you
do you like me?
I… I don’t know where...
where this is going.
It’s a yes or no question.
Yes, yes, I...
I like you.
Is that all?
And do you want to be with me?
What?
Just answer, please.
Okay then.
[footsteps]
Will you marry me?
It... It’s just that, I want to be
able to work here.
And earn more.
And...
just pay back my mom for all the
money that I owe her now. And I...
Of course, I want to be with you.
And... well, because of all of that,
- I spoke to an
immigration lawyer - - Wait.
You already reached out to a lawyer?
Well, yeah. And she said
that the fastest way for
me to get a work permit
was to marry a U.S. citizen.
Uh, I need, some...
some time to...
[dramatic music]